https://www.tjuc.org/website-privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Search for:
Thomas Jefferson Unitarian Church
A Community of Open Hearts, Inquiring Minds, and Helping Hands
Website Privacy Policy
This website is owned and operated by Thomas Jefferson Unitarian Church, referred to in this policy as “we”. We recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This privacy policy addresses those concerns. This policy may be changed or updated from time to time.
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at promotions@tjuc.org or debbie@tjuc.org. We are available to answer your questions or hear your concerns.
The first principle of Unitarian Universalism is to covenant to affirm and promote the inherent worth and dignity of every person. We believe that this principle impels us to protect the privacy of visitors.
Personal Information
Our site may collect personal information from our visitors only on a voluntary basis. Personal information may include name, address, phone number, email address, credit card numbers. We do not require this information to obtain access to any part of our site. We do not sell or rent this personal information to other organizations.
The personal information we collect is only used by us to process a request that has been placed by the visitor. We never sell your email address and if you voluntarily give it to us, we will strive to use it only for what it was intended. If we pass it, it would only be to the congregation or person who has the information you desire.
Statistical Information Collected
We collect information on the browsing habits of users and the companies that provide that service also have access to that information. This site collects information using cookies and javascript, so if they are enabled in your browser, information can be collected, such as your browser type, operating system, IP address, and country. This information is only used for statistical purposes and cannot identify you as an individual.
Information Accuracy
We make every effort to ensure that the information presented is correct and accurate. If inaccuracies occur, we will make every effort to correct them in a timely manner. To report any website inaccuracies or for questions about our Privacy Policy please email us at promotions@tjuc.org.
Links to Third Party Sites
Our web sites contain some hyperlinks to web sites operated by parties other than Thomas Jefferson Unitarian Church or Promotions Committee. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference only. We do not control such websites and are not responsible for their content nor privacy policies. The inclusion of hyperlinks to other websites does not imply any endorsement of the material on these Websites or any association with their operators.
Section Navigation
Recent News
WinterFair!
Virtual WinterFair! 2020 Recorded Live:: Video
December 6, 2020
Adult Learning Adult RE Committee Open Campus Classes
Preview :: Winter Open Campus 2021
December 2, 2020
Board of Trustees
Board Notes :: December 2020
December 2, 2020
June 2016
This SundayDecember 13, 2020 11:amBarb Friedland DLFE, TJUC PlayersJoin Service Here
Our traditional holiday season Lifespan Faith Engagement led service welcomes all ages into the story of “The Mitten Tree”, adapted from the book by Candace Christiansen. The service will feature familiar holiday music and some technology fun! Families and children … read more.
CategoriesCategories
Select Category
Adult Learning
Adult RE Committee
Asylum Family Project
Board of Trustees
Capital Campaign
Caring Ministry
Lifespan Learning
Mark Your Calendar!
Member Spotlight
Member Testimonials
Membership
Ministerial Updates
Music & Choir
Music Committee
Musical Notes
News & Events
Virtual WinterFair 2020
WinterFair!
4936 Brownsboro Rd
Louisville, KY 40222
Phone: (502) 425-6943
office@tjuc.org
Office hours: 9:30 am to 4:30 pm
Monday, Tuesday, Thursday, Friday
Member Directory
Our Interim Minister Please welcome our new interim minister, The Reverend Doctor Kathy Hurt. She has 30-years of experience in ministry with a doctorate in ministry from Meadville/Lombard Seminary.
Donate Today Help support us by making a donation. You can contact the office to set up deductions OR you can use the GivePlus Link. Establish your account only once and donate by CC, debit, or ACH withdrawal. Lower fees by using ACH to withdraw from your checking or savings acct. Thank you for your contribution.
GivePlus
© 2020 Thomas Jefferson Unitarian Church
Facebook Twitter YouTube Instagram
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Accessibility
InSpirit UU Books & Gifts
Log In
